[Music]
thank you
hello and welcome
very good morning to all the viewers
clearly if you see in terms of Market
the third consecutive session of decline
is what we are seeing however the cuts
are not that deep to join us in terms of
you know which stocks you should be
looking at from an investment
perspective we have a big Karma chief
executive officer at Rudy investment
joining in Vivek uh good morning and
welcome to the show
good morning
let's start off with firstly in terms of
the IT Major which is enforces the fall
was arrested in yesterday's session
after the Deep cuts that we saw today
again we are seeing some bit of pressure
that has started to build in as well uh
overall what's your view in terms of an
Infosys and would you advise an investor
to look at the counter at current levels
or would there be an alternate strategy
to play the It theme
was the I.T major TCS which announced
its results and uh that was okay sort of
uh results then uh came this uh I said
almost a bomb uh results by Infosys in
fact it bomb I should be here perfect in
my verdicts it bombed in the market and
the results were really pathetic
uh of course there are various factors
to it particularly because U.S is going
through a recession the spending in it
has reduced and the margins are under
pressure because inflation everywhere is
on the higher side but uh the and hence
the margins of these companies are under
severe pressure so Infosys did not come
out with a good set of results and that
brought the stock down on a single day
by 10 percentage and hence yesterday
what we saw was a value kind of buying
because after 10 percent uh and if you
look at technical charts also not just
fundamentals even technical charts
Infosys are some many times come around
this one one five zero one one six zero
levels and given a bounce back from
there so whenever it made a panic law it
was during this around these levels 1160
levels wherein it posed from so I feel
uh if somebody really wants to enter it
have a typescope of Atlas for 12 months
because what I feel is the interest rate
cycle has stopped I don't think there is
going to be big hikes from here maximum
0.25 percentage from here and that will
stabilize the U.S economy so it will
take 12 months at least so you can buy
here the stop loss of 1160 because uh
that's a great support and uh in 12
months we might see approximately say 10
to 12 10 to 15 percentage of returns
from here that's quite possible because
the evaluations have actually followed
up
Right Moving on you have a shipping Corp
of India which is seeing some smart
gains in today's session as well now
overall if you see uh in terms of the
news around it firstly there has been a
circuit revision you know in terms of
the counter overall probably a lot of
chatter going around with regards to it
being a divestment Target as well uh
what would you advise as an investor to
do with the shipping Corporation of
India
this is a great company but in wrong
hands wrong hands in the sense uh
government's job is not doing business
and this government is very very clear
that uh our business is not to win the
business so they only have to govern and
hence uh wherever possible in fact today
we are seeing the beml bharata was
limited that has demerged uh into land
parcel separate yes whatever land assets
they have and The Core Business separate
so similar process is going on in the
shipping Corporation also wherein
shipping business would be demolished
separately and all the assets of the
company will get demons separately and
that government will hold and the
business alone might get divested so
once that happens I think uh shipping
Corporation is super undervalued at
these prices uh if you look at the
movement of other companies for a
particularly G shipping this stock has
not been not given any returns to
reinvestors but the core business is
very very good so I think one should buy
with a short-term Target of one or four
uh that is possible which is almost 10
percent from here because the stock is
at 92.94 right now so 104 could be a
reasonable uh Target but uh one caveat
over here uh we are talking about D
merger and diverse mid emerging might
happen but because that's uh in
government's head but divestment can
take time uh at times for example Concor
Container Corporation that's diverse
Windows going on last three years
government is serious about it but
Market is not supporting it so that can
delay the divestment process but the
stock is very good if your absolute
long-term investor yes you should hold
it
right so that's with regards to shipping
Corp of India now another angle that I
want to take into consideration from a
sector perspective is the Alcove
companies now as we know now that the
Delhi is refusing to renew Corners legal
sale license now one thing is that every
state has to you know I mean the company
has to procure the license from every
state now to my understanding this is
pertaining only to Delhi right now now
if the license does not get renewed do
you think this can add to the benefit of
the Indian manufacturers and Indian
alcohol companies and if so what would
your view be
is going on right for a similar kind of
uh corruption charges which is uh even
this company is accused of so this is
more of politics I feel and uh what I
feel is uh if not today maybe a month or
two later the licenses will get uh
renewed because uh the whole company or
the whole business will not get stopped
as such and liquor business is one such
which is Lifeline or we can say oxygen
uh line for any government I I am
speaking to you from Chennai and the
biggest Revenue to the tamilnadu
government comes from again uh liquor
business so this is one common phenomena
across India so this could be a
temporary thing and due to that there
are some stocks which are going down but
liquor as such I find that longer term
should be very very good over here and
if you look at the uh say population to
the consumption ratio of liquor India
stands nowhere in cities we might find
that if almost everybody is drinking but
uh the Leisure drinking will still pick
up more and I think the ratio is too low
in India and hence uh this is a space
which is for absolute long term yeah
this kind of political headache will
continue happening and once this sector
also comes under GST now that's a
it will happen but yeah once it comes
into GST this sector can actually do
very very well so my favorite pick in
this space would be uh United Spirits uh
though there are brokerage reports today
undervaluing this talk is but giving a
lower Target of around 650 but I feel uh
stock should not go below 700 it's a
great uh company and it was a Vijay male
company and was taken over by diigo and
diju has cleaned the books totally and
they are focusing on early on
premiumization right now so this stock
should do well over a period of time
Right Moving on your ICICI Lombard which
reported numbers as well now clearly if
you see in terms of the performance
that's been satisfactory however there's
been the reaffirmation in terms of the
guidance goes at almost 102 percent uh
cor by F525 and this is despite the
dynamic Regulatory and insurance Market
environment now how are you looking at
ICICI Lombard and from a valuation
perspective as well what would you
advise that investor to do
I'm giving you stop loss here because
though actually stop loss is not
required it's a great company but uh
1050 should be a stop loss because
markets can get very very volatile
nowadays so results were satisfactory
and I feel this is one space we should
keep growing but uh the insurance sector
assets is under pressure right now
because there's irda
uh say investigation going on wherein
the allegations are that these companies
have been paying uh more to the uh
Brokers and even to the banks in fact uh
today is one of the leading newspapers
uh is carrying this story on the front
page itself so that uh pressure is still
uh mounting on those companies but
overall uh General space I think will
continue growing by minimum 50 to 18
percentage uh going in future also so
it's a 10-year story but uh short term
also yeah I feel it can be a 1500 stock
so 1050 should be a good stop loss that
you should buy
right so that's with regards to where
icsa and Lombard goes moving only of the
Pharma pack which has been up and about
in trade for a second consecutive
session and the moment specifically with
the DB's Laboratories is really strong
uh how are you looking at a devious
Laboratories in trade Vivek because uh
in terms of the stock price as well last
one month almost 19 to 20 is the kind of
upside that we've already seen in this
counter
uh here I am in fact enjoying the Pharma
moment because uh just ten days back we
invested in Pharma and made our clients
also in question a lot of form of mutual
funds as well so everything is up
everybody's happy Market is not doing
good but our foreign
[Music]
company these stock prices are lower and
they give you space of almost say 20
Rally from here very very easily so if
you want to buy a smaller of course you
this is the best bet you should
definitely enter into it and if somebody
really wants to go into say contrary and
Pharma stock biocon also is looking
amazingly well after this kind of
Direction so the downside should be very
very limited but the upside can be 15 20
very easy
right so that's the farmer's backpack as
a whole metal stocks have been up in
trade as well and this is mainly on the
back of the impact of dollar which is
below the one zero one Mark already now
you know this is pretty much cyclical
you know a lot of ups and downs that
we've seen in the last three to four
months with regards to metal counters uh
what would your view be from here on
is a cyclical bit and and a lot depends
on how China performs from here so uh
one there are there are two ways to look
at it if China opens up fully starts uh
say the demand of metal sector and the
prices go up the metal companies will do
well but that has a negative effect
effect on the uh Indian economy because
we are consuming a lot of metal right
now for our infrastructure needs and
that again puts up inflationary pressure
on the uh government budgets so it's a
double-edged sword so I feel uh better
should overall do market performance uh
from here not outperform it just would
be a market performance but after this
correction uh from tops for example I'm
saying chart of Tata steel from 124 it
came or below 100 and is trading at 109
today so this kind of stocks look good
maybe for a seven to eight percent rally
overall and uh
aluminum would be my first bet over here
two reasons one is a metal and the other
is a lot of uh play the EV space as well
so aluminum should be the number one uh
pet so if I have to name stocks I think
nalco and Talco really looks good so
overall uh metal will be market
performance a performer here not
outperforming right and very lastly one
more sector that's coming to my eye
right now is the rice stocks you know
krbl Kohinoor Foods as well as uh
healthy foods all the three counters are
up in trade and there has been a report
with regards to a global rice shortage
and this would be the biggest one in the
last 20 years I think it's a report by
Fitch that's coming in uh if this
continues how are you expecting rice
companies to move overall because it's
not only from a demand domestic Market
perspective but even from an export
perspective if you see uh if shortage is
going to lead to price hikes uh how does
it impact margins
if all this rice Compares two two parts
to it uh one is all this rice companies
have corrected uh significantly and
hence
say even if this news is not there they
might give you a 10 rise so this is one
thing second thing yes we are talking
about El Nino effect this year and uh
some sort of shortage of raids all this
will make rice prizes uh Stay High
but uh here I love when we talk about
exports
say we also have 140 145 crore
population which has to be fed right and
government is very very clear uh they
already have restrictions on exports and
I don't think they're going to allow
this companies to export freely the
similar story like sugar what is
happening so uh I cannot be very bullish
on these stocks as I said for no reason
also they have to move 10 because they
are corrected a lot but if you think
they are going to really outperform here
I don't think so because the
restrictions on export will stay here
and government would not take the risk
of exporting the rice available in India
and then uh seeing the rice Brothers
shoot in India and next year is budget I
mean sorry not budget your looks of
Elections so that will be always kept in
mind when it comes to agree products so
10 rally is fine but don't expect say a
lottery out of it
right so that's with regards to a
short-term rally that could come in in
terms of price counters and a short-term
bet that Vivek is indicating thank you
Vivek so much for joining us on the show
and giving us those views with regards
to what should be done with all the
movers and shakers in trade today thank
you stay safe and speak to you soon
again
thanks
[Music]